Kamal Kumar Patel () Featured

Having 9.3 years of IT experience which includes 2.5 years of experience in Blue Prism and 1.8 years in UiPath. Currently working as a senior UiPath developer. Certified as Advanced RPA Developer by UiPath. Certified as Blue Prism Developer.



Current Designation: Senior Consultant Total Experience: 9 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Saama Technologies Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Chennai, Bengaluru / Bangalore, Pune
Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: RPA, Blueprism, Blue Prism, UiPath, Robotic Process Automation, UiPath Certified, Blue Prism Certified

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Having 9.3 years of IT experience, which includes 2.5 years of experience in Blue Prism and 1.8 years in UiPath. Certified as Advanced RPA Developer by UiPath. Certified as Blue Prism Developer. Currently working as a senior UiPath developer.

5 years of experience in Core Java and J2EE frameworks.

Work Experience

Saama Technologies as Senior Consultant May 2019 to Till Date

Currently working as a senior UiPath developer. I also have 2.5 years of experience in Blue Prism.

Infosys as Technology Analyst May 2015 to May 2019

2.5 years of experience as a Blue Prism developer.

Hexaware Technologies as Software Engineer Sep 2011 to Apr 2015

3.5 years of experience as a Java developer.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Biju Patnaik University of Technology (BPUT) in 2011

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

UiPath Advanced RPA Developer

Blue Prism Developer Certified

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience	
Blue Prism	6	2019	2 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
Uipath	2019.10	2020	1 Year(s) 6 Month(s)	
JAVA, J2EE	7	2016	5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert			
Hindi	Expert			
Odia	Expert			

Projects

Project Title: Onboarding and managing new Trading Partner

Client: Genentech Solutions
Nature of Employment: Full Time

Role: Sr. Programmer Skill Used: UiPath

Role Description: Senior RPA Developer

Project Details: Genentech is an American biotechnology corporation which develops medicines and provides to the customers through hundreds of trading partners. We are implementing RPA in modules like onboarding a new trading partner, managing data into multiple downstream systems, extracting reports on daily basis etc. This also includes implementation of business rules across different systems.

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time

Duration: Feb 2020 - Nov 2020

Onsite / Offsite: Offsite